{"questions":[{"question":"What can't we achieve with software testing","level":"2","answers":["Reveal as many errors as possible","Identify bugs","Behavioral tests","Determine that there are no bugs in the software"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"What isn't a consideration when we design","level":"2","answers":["Where is the interaction taking place","How did the user hear about our product","What activities are being carried out","Who the users are"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"What is the first rule in interface design","level":"2","answers":["Know your user","Make unique designs","Use contrasting colours","Try to do your best"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"What is the visibility consideration in interface design","level":"2","answers":["The code should be written in small letters so people can't copy it","Secure the users data and encrypt them so they are not visible","How clearly does the user see the user interface, its state and the possible options","Can the user be seen while using our app"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"What is a software systemâ\u20AC™s architecture","level":"3","answers":["Is the set of principal design decisions","The material that is used to construct it","How many developers do we have in each team","The coding language we use in a product"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"How is Agile planning different from the traditional approach to planning? ","level":"3","answers":["Agile planning is done only once","Agile planning is non iterative","Agile planning places emphasis on the plan","Agile planning places emphasis on planning and is iterative"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"Which of the following is correct list of classifications of design patterns.","level":"3","answers":["Creational, Structural and Behavioral patterns.","Executional, Structural and Behavioral patterns.","Creational, Executional and Behavioral patterns.","None of the above."],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"Which type of design patterns are specifically concerned with object creation mechanisms?","level":"2","answers":["Creational Design Patterns","Structural Design Patterns","Behavioral Design Pattern","Concurrency Pattern"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"Who is responsible for prioritizing the product backlog?","level":"2","answers":["Project Manager","Product Owner","Lead Developer","Tester"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"Which of the following is not defined in a good Software Requirement Specification (SRS) document?","level":"2","answers":["Functional Requirement","Nonfunctional Requirement","Goals of implementation","Algorithm for software implementation"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"Software Requirement Specification (SRS) is also known as specification of _______","level":"2","answers":["White box testing","Acceptance testing","Black box testing","Integrated testing"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"MVC is composed of three components. These are:","level":"1","answers":["Member Vertical Controller","Model Variable Centered","Model View Controller","Member Vertical Controller"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"Which of the following is an essential concept related to Cloud?","level":"3","answers":["Reliability","Abstraction","Productivity","All of the above"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"In the Planning Phase, Which of the following is the correct step for performing the analysis?","level":"2","answers":["Cloud Computing Value Proposition","Cloud Computing Strategy Planning","Both A and B","Business Architecture Development"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"The modification of the software to match changes in the ever changing environment, falls under which category of software maintenance?","level":"2","answers":["Corrective","Adaptive","Perfective","Preventive"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"2"},{"question":"_______ measures the ability of a regression test selection technique to handle realistic applications","level":"2","answers":["Efficiency","Precision","Generality","Inclusiveness"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"3"},{"question":"When should code review take place?","level":"1","answers":["Every other week","When the product is finished","After the customer received the product","After each development iteration"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"4"},{"question":"When does the documentation phase occur?","level":"1","answers":["It is always done before iteration ends","When the code is sent to production","After a bug is fixed","After requirements are set"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"1"},{"question":"  ","level":"1","answers":["It satisfies its specification","You get an A+ on it","It is delivered on time","It is robust"],"team":"Husky","correct_ans":"1"}]}